out the show star shine is so bright watch the secrets unfold there's magic in her hands
whisper what the future holds
We are Kangol
Wanna close out for lies, tricks, plot and chaos with those cosmic eyes
Lola's squeening on the chair, Rudy got flare
Marbles in the mix, we don't play fair
Chat blowing up like divine confessions
True bombs drop, no time for confessions
You on logic, we bend it, drama, we mend it
Panel full of chaos, but the vibe's transcending
If a troll wanna bark, we clap back politely
With Andromalius, watchin' nightly
Prophecy and cosmic mistakes Alissa in the chat, she a mystery queen
DJ Electric got the beat so clean Beater with the panther, strength divine
She teams chaos with the stare and the line We don't do fake, this trap's too real
We roast you kindly, but the love's a deal Got minds with swords keeping gates tight
They swing truth like justice in the moon like Gifted subs, yeah the coke keeps growing
Welcome to Psych Awaken's TV
It's crazy, it's loud, it's bizarre, believe me
We laugh, we scream, we read the unseen
Father, psych, the cat, daddy, king of the stream
Welcome to Psych Awaken's TV
With truth and madness, sip the same tea
It's a family affair, it's dysfunction supreme
You just woke up in a lucid dream
Cards flip, candles drip, shadows in the mist
Trolls, dogs lick, but they cease to exist
We're half chaos half oracle flame and every night to ritual and psyches name no scripts no filters
No chill inside we stream raw truth to the morning light. So grab your tea grab your mic and buy
This ain't YouTube, this is an underworlds talk show, you are now initiated.
Father Psyche is spoken, spoken.
You make the chat feel like
I like my shave.
I shaved, because finally I went one day
without somebody saying, oh, you have a turkey neck
or something, so I was like, okay.
Oh, yeah, what do you want to say hi, Lolo?
You just purr in my lap.
You have a little RBF, or you might RBF cat.
I'm just gonna change the name to RBF.
and you're just making that babe?
Can you smile?
Oh, there you go.
Okay, babe.
You see tricks over there?
Hey, babe.
What'd it do?
What do you say?
What the?
What do you mean what the?
What are you talking about?
What the what?
Hey, okay, so you're ready for a premiere, guys?
I haven't premiered a premiere of the new song in a while.
So then I can play it later,
because no one's ever gonna see it.
["You and Ghosts With Your Hair Loved In"]
Airplane mode, I felt it in my skin
So I was sitting like designer gold
And let a stranger's body keep me cool
You know the spark, you know the gun
You pull the string, I come undone
You say you love to watch me burn
Baby, pain's the only thing we need
Not to be solicitous, but the way you left was biblical
So I did something ritual, cause grief for me is silicone
I might have sent a picture from a mortal bed
Just to haunt you, goddamn it
I knew you craved the chaos I fit
Cause love like all they never did
Not to be divine, but I love you
It's fair, every wound you gave I will
We take turns being the villains' muse
But damn it, I still wanna lose
Not to be celestial, but you made my pain perpetual
So I did something sexual, just to feel conceptual
Not to be divine, but I love you
What was never spoken
Every scar, a holy mark
Every kiss, another spark
Not to be divine
He smiled with the frowning.
We're bashing?
Who are we bashing?
Was that bashing anybody?
It wasn't intended to.
It's actually based on a song called
Not To Be Dramatic, But I Love You
or something like that.
I changed the words around.
I think that is.
Yeah, I'm not really
even in the mood to bash.
I don't even think
we know what I did
Baby, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I think I did do a song about the Rapture though, did I?
I don't know if I did, but I did make something though.
Here, let's check it out.
That's really on the night, okay?
I'm just, I'm just learning stuff, still.
TV Tony did thinking I was ghost. Oh my god
See hey, always smile. Hey Jamie. Hey, they can give him with a new thing on YouTube painting. Yeah, so it's like
Kind of like I can actually during the show I can turn it to like members only show
And what will happen is that everybody's a member will continue on through the show
And then I think, well, this is just what you two told me.
And then it's like anybody that's not a member,
they'll get a message on the screen that says,
hey, continue, and you can turn the membership.
I think the membership is a relatively pretty good deal
because they'll get at least one detailed reading.
You know, of course they'll get more readings, right?
Especially anytime a member asks,
I'll probably be very quick to read for them.
One, uh, one detail long long like long reading a month and then plus all the other
Billions of things I'm gonna need to change the emojis around a little bit, but I do have some fucking I
Think I got some of the best emojis on YouTube guys. I don't know. I think I got kind of like some of the
Like a little bit of rare find on YouTube, right? I
Don't find channels I like very much like all the time. Well, you know
you guys channels I want to see but
It's like, you know, there's just a few people I talk with, like, watching other shows, right?
I'm not even necessarily...
They don't even like me that. Some of this was only to like me pretty much, but...
But, uh...
If you ever want to know how to, like, succeed on the channels,
I'm not saying I'm having some huge success story, but I'll say...
I'm absolutely, 100% satisfied with where I've gone with the channel, I know.
I'm fine with it, but I think I have a million people in a year, right?
I was very realistic as in saying I thought I would have less than a thousand for maybe a year.
And how long did it take?
Think I I don't know. I think I did like almost like a thousand and one month without subscribers. I'm at
375,000 or something watch hours. Just think about how many watch hours
That is like people three hundred seventy five thousand hours of my show like just think of like because it's all the people that watch
Like you know different so like all the people times like whatever they watch right and all that consciousness
And think of like we bring it consciousness like together in that kind of sense and like you know
like probably make cool things happen if we like
you know
Have like, you know a heart to it like no, that's why it's always good things
But hey everybody, let me see. Oh, who's back? Oh, so nobody's backstage
Yeah
That's like the thing is like
Think about like how how like the heart is like considered evil
The Bible says the heart is evil and has evil desires and stuff like that
But it's like thinking about if we didn't have a heart like I mean, it's like
So it has to be like both sides of it, right?
It has to be like, you know, it can like, you know, lead us to like sadness and things they can break and that's the worst part
but it also is like
Like
Feels right. It's like that part of the I feel in my heart more than my head really, but my head I like
Just like, you know, I'm a very like fast thinker, right?
think like
Too fast and I think really weirdly abstract a little bit, but not like
Like always in a good way of like where I was with the capricorn stuff
It's like that I can function in the world in a way
But I still did have some hard time functioning in the regular world, right?
I mean, but I functioned fine in the world where it's like, you know, we can be the free beings and like,
you know, free spirits and things, but it's like I'm not really great in like the
structure. I could not really wake up at the same time every day.
I like that. I just need to like be able to sleep as long as I need to sleep, be awake as long as I need to be awake and
you know, not have to worry about, oh, I have to be here at this time, to be here at this time.
Just do the show what I want. I mean I did take a shower and put on like underwear like
So today
But I felt like it I could basically just be like make it from the waist down and you would never know
That's my that would be working. Okay, I could actually and it's like I was like
Amazing, you know that amazing thought I like the thought of making money in my sleep, too. Like I wish I have done
because I was booking readings in my sleep.
You're pledging $100,000?
Thank you, Gotti.
Okay, can we get a notary here right away, please?
Okay.
He was mad at Samman for winning $5
but I'm on the panel and he pledged to grant
to psyche out of spite.
Hold on.
Someone pledged to $1,000?
Well, you know, good.
And so Samman, just remember me.
Just remember, like, you know.
That no matter like and you are never like really like, you know cool to me or anything
you're kind of like a
Little bit of a silly person, but I like that about you. It's like, you know, you have kind of like a
You know pretty silly your lap is like so I mean, but it's kind of funny, but it's like
I can't even do it, but oh my god.
But yeah, and then you do, you know,
people seem to like you, like you was on the panel today,
like playing like some 80s music and stuff like that.
You know, kind of doing what I kind of like do,
like music and stuff like that, except when I do it,
you know, everyone leaves the room and I'm like,
I look up and there's like zero people in the room.
And he just still had a hundred people
that are chilling with him and it's like, okay, well.
I think I need to work on my likability a little bit,
a little bit.
I don't think I've seen anybody with as big as a show I have,
have so few likes, like it's like I have like,
sometimes I have less than 10.
Okay, and I used to be on Amazon,
so just you do a fit check at like a hundred likes
and like, should we just say,
oh, I'll stand up and turn around once and then,
you know, and then everyone would like get to it
in like five minutes and stuff like that, right?
I have no idea how it would like it to be.
Every time I say, like the stream, people dislike it.
And then there's like a bad ratio of dislikes.
And I'm like, that can't be good.
I don't know how to survive on YouTube.
I must be doing something right because,
I mean, what hasn't been said on the show?
I mean, what hasn't been seen, said,
I mean, it's like everything.
You know, Slurdy Diamond has gotten naked on the show and Samann
Strokes his this red balloon on the air one. You know, Janet
twerked in her thong
and then you know, somewhere in Marcy and
Spunky I'll show their boobs one night, you know kind of like to cover in their nipples. Yeah, absolutely
you know
it was pretty much
Everything else, right?
I don't think anyone left like in a bad mood then, you know, it's just like, it's just like a fun event, right?
So, I mean
And I'm survived with all that
Bookbuckers and sea chickens are NFL replay. There's a band, there's a team called the Sea Chickens
I never heard of the NFL team called the Sea Chickens, but you know what?
I'm a sea bull, I'm from the, this thing called the bestia neptunus, or bestia, oh neptunus,
which is like some sea monster.
Basically that white bull from like, you know, Crete, that, you know, he was supposed
to sacrifice this white bull, but he's like, he liked the white bull so much, and he was
so beautiful that he just wanted to keep it, like, in his cabin, stable.
Her name is Pasifay? Yeah, Pasifay. He cursed the wife to fall in love with the bull, and so Pasifay hired like this like kind of like, you know, the Bill Nye or the guy, I don't know, they're kind of like wacky and ventured and needless to like build this suit that she could like, you know, have sex with the, she could like, you know.
Get into this suit and then she could have sex with the bull because it's like it was like a bowl outfit
You know, it's kind of like that one where it's like takes two people and like one has to be like that
But it was like I don't know he like such a great artificer that I don't I don't think she had to have more than one person
in the, you know, the bull sex toys that he made.
But anyway, she got an ad, she got pregnant.
Can you imagine how painful that would be
with that bull?
They have these big horns, right?
And so, yeah, it was a terrible, terrible labor and stuff.
But, you know, and then they have Minotaur,
and it's like, you know, he was kind of special, you know?
I don't know, it's like, he's like that.
family member we don't really talk about and stuff but yeah so he got like you
know basically put inside this like labyrinth I don't think he was like that
bad of a guy his name was a stereo and he was a very very good looking
bull but he was like half human so of course he's gonna be like someone
attractive but then like the the whole bull part of it makes it a little like
But anyway, it was a very good looking bull, but nobody wanted to hit the fuck with him.
So he put him in the labyrinth, in the middle of the labyrinth, and then some hero came
and like, there's this, yeah, the beautiful daughter named Ariadne.
And Ariadne taught the hero, I think it's the end of the thesis, she taught the hero how to get through the labyrinth, which is basically, she gave him a clue, this is where the word clue comes from, but it's actually a clue, means like a thread, like a spool of thread, it's a clue, right?
Maybe it's a clue, right? So she's like, okay, well basically you can figure it out, you just like, you know, follow the thread and like tie it to something and then find your way out.
When she did and he slayed the bull, and then, yeah, but I think he was kind of a dick, I don't know what happened to him.
Yeah, he was supposed to like marry Ariadne and take her, but then he like, you know, just like left during the night when she fell asleep or something like that, and she was very pissed about that.
Who wouldn't be? She would, you know. Plus she's a princess, and then why would you do that?
I've been on it. I believe I have been on it.
They took a cruise one day in Greece, but I lived in Greece for like a month, but most of the time was with the family.
They're a very nice family. I love the mother. The mother like...
It was like treated me like a real son. She was like, you know, just very heavy said like older woman
She was like they had a restaurant and she was like this
Amazing cook like oh my god. I love like the stuff peppers and like she was just like, you know the best meals and the big family
Thanks, and everyone spoke Greek, and I like hardly spoke anything, but I was like a novelty because I
Was American plus I was like bleach blonde hair
I was tall, I was skinny, I was very gay and ready to like fucking play the field.
Yeah, like that's how I was like 15 years old I think.
And I was so excited to go to Greece because I thought it would be like, I had read about
like, you know, the gladiator, you know, I thought it was like some kind of like, everyone
was bisexual and gorgeous, it kind of are, you know, that's not an untrue stereotype,
but they're very much less, you know, out in the open about it.
would have hoped but so yeah so I was kind of like you know I got called Malacca
you know F-H-E-G-O-T and like you know by people because I was very I can show
you pictures sometime Alex owes me something I heard I saw Alex in in a
who's chat was he on he's on Samans and he's pretty rude to Saman but it's like
you know
He's at least Alex is at least like somewhat funny like that guy a rando who always come calls in he called
Sam and in the n-word like very directly and like a couple times and in a really like mean way and with the really
Accentuated kind of like hard R. Like and it's like it's just like so nasty. It's like and it's on the
Trip kick rumble. I don't want us to play it on my show because it's just like too ugly, but it's like
Like I didn't know that guy was like that like it's like I mean it's like it's I
Get a lot of flak for like
People I have on my show right like the only I was gonna blame for others like something has nothing to do with me except for like
You know me sitting here and talking to people, but yeah, you know
You've had all types of people here, you know, like I think a bit like people can
Share what they believe and it's like if they're ignorant or like it will be pretty much evident like and then
You can go oh my god. I'm glad I don't think like that or oh my gosh
I kind of you know, there's different points people can make that we might agree or disagree with but
It's always good to have like a lot of
diverse
Points to because it's not like great is like the freedom to like actually just everyone can believe what they want to believe
And not everyone has to believe the same thing and it's like and then that would cause all kinds of extra
Trouble and compulsions and stuff. You keep seeing the light of the light of a TV show
Is I think oh, it's I think it's because of my I have windows on my big screen TV right here
And then I have like the bar on the bottom is like this beautiful
Blue color, I don't see here
Say hi yourself
You see the TV
I don't see it, I don't see it, I don't see it.
Hey, I can kind of see a bit.
I don't know, there's a blue line, right?
I don't know, you can't, I don't know
if you can't see it perfectly, but hold on,
that's just what I can do right now.
Oh, oh, because I'm not on full screen, hold on.
Why is that, how long has that been on?
You can tell me, I was like, in this little screen,
I was like, where am I?
I thought, okay, that's right, okay, remove that.
There's poison under the think, of course.
Ooh, yeah, I drank, we had a housekeeper who left out
like the lemon pledge or something on the floor
when I was like, you know, baby, this is like two years old.
And I like, my older brother was like probably 11 or 12,
came home from school.
And he just saw me like on the floor convulsing and stuff and I remember that's one of my first memories
I remember thinking oh, this is apple juice, and it's like you know in a nice fancy bottle
And I was like and then I just like started drinking it but it was like floor cleaning it right there's like
Lemon pledge or maybe something worse. Hopefully not something worse, but um
Yeah, so I had to get my stomach pumped for that and then I had another like thing where
I couldn't like hold down food and I would just like projectile vomit everything
Which is like really not very pleasant like for people to have to like you know
Clean up and like you know when they're in beat especially and it's kind of scary for you know
And then they the doctors were telling my mom like that she was like, you know, basically a munch house and like they're like
Oh, well, you're are you like, you know, you're kind of like over over concerned about it
He's just like he'll probably be fine or something and then like but I was like losing a lot of weight and
They just can they just didn't know what was going on like they couldn't but then they had figured out a few years before like the
the thing it was like it was like a
close-up esophagus and so there's a surgery for it then and
But I had no veins at the time and so they had to or they these the veins in my head
And I was like so there's pictures of me as a baby like with all these like IVs in my head and
Yeah, and that's so that's gonna be why I'm so skinny
See what are you guys talking about Indonesia?
So yeah, they look good with oh my gosh. Yeah, I do have the kind of I hope I don't have a turkey neck
But it's like, you know, I don't know women that kind of like
Very is it very long is that like a longer than normal neck or it seems like it's kind of long right now
Is that long or is it just me?
Okay, it's weird look how big my Adam's apple is there's like a whole like
entire like
Pardon me
Like I mean that's like I'm definitely a man like imagine if you saw a woman and she had this kind of Adam's apple
That is like a big Adam's apple. What do you think guys? Maybe that's what gets a little looks it looks like a face right there
Kind of to doesn't look like a face in there
Isn't that weird? Oh, creepy.
Hey, witch, Mary, you're picturing the Exorcist?
Well, I didn't really care for those movies.
They're a little bit too, like, orthodox.
Like, I get kind of bored with, like, all the,
kind of, like, the religious part of it.
But what's he building in there?
Okay, so...
Yeah, I'm sorry if I'm not keeping up with the chat very well. I've just had an interesting day. Oh, I got some McDonald's
So that I have some weed. I have oh, I've got drinks, too. I got a couple of
the
hurricane punches
So
Who's building wet where?
Like is somebody building something in the chat. Can we all move there? Is it a compound for the
psyche awakens cult? I
need to
I need some, you know, some property
Some property we can all go live there all of us. I
Can get them shaved off now. I want to keep the
I want to keep my yeah, it's just weird without any of them there and because then I don't know
Call master bedroom. Okay. We can also be a big bed. That's what I thought. That's how I picture it
You just push a bunch of mattresses together and then like all 50 of us can
Maybe not have a bunk beds. We could have like that'd be kind of fun. No
Yeah, oh, I don't really want to do that. I don't want I don't want to have a sex cult
We're talking about Canada dry is being a unique butterfly. Okay Canada dries building something and
He's not he just doesn't want to share what it is a whole he has he's building there. He heard someone moaning
Oh, see? Well, it's not Sam-Man because he's Sam-Man's in a different place, and so he can't be over here.
He definitely has never been over here. Never. I'm telling the truth. Guys, this is how rumors get started. Stop. Stop saying I'm confused too, Mary.
I'm confused too.
Which Mary, do you know I have a relative
that was executed in the Connecticut witch trials?
Kind of interesting.
Canada Drivers is doing his thing.
Let me just put this microphone closer.
How does this sound to that?
Let me check.
Make sure the correct microphone is on.
I should have taken my equipment beforehand.
And it is not on correctly.
I had my webcam mic on.
Hello?
Can you hear me better now?
So I'll try to hold this closer.
DJ Electra
I wish I could sing like that person in the song. She kind of sounds like Sia
What do you think?
Your mother was a witch?
Yeah, my grandmother was like kind of like not I
Wouldn't say I mean she wasn't like really religious. I mean I just don't know but I would say yeah, you know
I she was very like, you know
She was a doll maker. I mean she's kind of witchy right she made a doll named Michael
It was really creepy and then she had a doll room
And then she would have guests sleep in the doll room and like people wouldn't want to sleep in that because there's bunch of dolls in there
Like looking at you. They're all like
And they're all like, you know, and then oh my god, those cabbage patch were so ugly and she thought they were cute
Now what's the sound from underneath the door? He's pounding nails into a hardwood floor
Oh, are you doing like an Edgar Allen Poe kind of thing or like a
Are you evil? I
Don't know. Are you good? I have another song. I'll put another song
I don't know. It isn't good and evil like kind of like two sides of something. I don't know
through shadows, heart wrapped in chains, a mortal soul aching, tethered to pain, whispers
of a love she could never see, a hidden hand guiding her destiny, from the gold
Unseen, a God of desire in shadows between Cupid's wings beating against fate's cruel
One spark, one touch, could ignite it all Forbidden fire, 1110
A mortal girl and a God, a name
Through trials and terror, the darkness they fight
Two hearts collided
In the edge of night, sight, rise on wings of light
Love is a storm in the endless night
We climb eternal stars beyond space and time
You've been striped with your unseen hand
Lift us all, make us understand
The mortal heart, the immortal flame
Bound by love, forever the same
I really like what I just made too. I think you guys missed it.
Airplane mode I felt it in my skin
So I was sitting like designer gold
And let a stranger's body keep me cool
You know the spark, you know the gun
You pull the string, I come undone
You say you love to watch me burn
Baby, pain's the only thing we need
Not to be celestial, but the way you left was biblical
So I did something ritual, cause grief for me is silicone
I might have sent a picture from a mortal bed
Just to haunt you goddamn head
I knew you craved the chaos I fed
Cause love like alls ain't never dead
Not to be divine, but I love you
Even when I want to curse you
I could never
It's fair, every wound you gave I wear
We take turns being the villains' muse
But damn it, I still wanna lose
Not to be celestial, but you made my pain perpetual
So I did something sexual, just to feel conceptual
I'm not gonna lie, I'm not gonna lie
Not to be divine, but I love you
Don't forget what was never spoken
Every scar, a holy mark
Every kiss, another spark
Not to be divine
I'll make you a mod, Mary, because you need a talented witch by my side, and I think you
might fit the bill, just do me a favor and curse anybody that fucks with us, right?
Deal?
Hey, JD, how are you?
And please don't curse the mods.
Okay, let's see.
Or me, of course.
I'm gonna pin link
and mod
or a resident
which, your name is which.
Oh, it's a which, okay.
That's fine to say.
I love having
Wonderful people around. Okay. Oh JT. Why aren't you a mod? Definitely a mod
I mean, you can't have rain be a mod and not you and then Mary. Okay, got you
Because that would be that would be kind of like cause problems in your in your relationship, wouldn't it? Let me see. Um
Okay, there you go
That'll be $50 Mary. I'm just I'm just kidding
It only makes it doesn't make sense. I don't know but JT if you mod with your feelings, okay?
Don't okay?
It's only fear because I am a mod at the
CFF
Did you know I was a model over there? I didn't remember I ever went there, but I did one time and I became a mod
Must have liked me at one point. So let's keep that energy up
Okay, so I need to pin my link. Okay one second
but I guess, okay.
I'm sorry, I'm smoking this garlic cookie's weed
and it's really strong.
And so I might fall asleep.
I'm sorry if I do, I'm just a little,
you know, I get really, I may get really stoned.
And so sometimes I get kind of quiet or mumbly
and so I'll try not to do that.
What's next entertain you okay? I mean I have like I'm trying to make like new music every day
I really thought that was good, but I keep wanting to play like the oh, yeah, I didn't know I did I played that one
I can't play everything. I want I have the uh, let me see what else I have
I have to kind of like go back and download some of the stuff and find stuff because
When I deleted or reinstall windows, I didn't bring my documents over or anything over and so and so
Not everything was saved like I should have been but it's like all over the Internet
I can probably go find like 99% of it, but I
Just don't have it all hands right now. So let me see. I have I got some new sound effects. You're gonna hear them here
Listen to this
That's like a laugh, okay, did you hear that over this one?
That's pretty good
This is a high-pitched man screaming
Okay, pretty good. I mean, I don't know why I picked these. I mean, I did customize these
I don't know why I picked this particular one, but
That's a good one, like, you know, for that, um, the explosion one, I like that, and it was like the slide whistle.
And this one, so I said, say, oh my god, like, I think I was trying to say, like, gay, oh my god, or something like that.
But look at that, look how it sounds.
Oh my god.
Okay.
So that didn't quite work, okay.
Then I said, sexy woman saying, mmm.
Mmm.
Okay, got that how about I love big granny panties
That's what sound came out of that I don't know it's like I just you know it's weird and this one says help me Jesus
I said he helped me Jesus
Jesus, okay, that's what that one said, okay, and then I said hype. Okay, then there's more high-pitched
I scream okay. Oh Satan laughing
Okay, another one
Okay, that's all I have so far I mean, I'm sorry it's like not that great, but
But I got Priya
That's a good one. I'll play the gaudi song. Okay, do you want to see the gaudi song? Did everyone see that one?
The Gotti song. Gotti loves the song.
Out of New York, came a storm on wheels, rolling in smooth with a mafia feels, Cuban cigar, lit like it's temper, pizza in one hand, hot dog for dinner said psyche, I'm bored, had to switch the scene, left some poor woman screaming on live stream, trolled her down to the void and back, then crashed my show like a heart attack, gotty, made man, troking my-
But they're still my friends
Yeah, love, you got it
Till the bitter end we fight
We troll, but we friends
Forever my friend
Things he's got with the lowercase g in a wheelchair still stomping through the live feed
Bout of your king while smoking that leaf
Laughing at chaos like it's comic relief brought spunky too now that trolls a gem mean one sweet ones
They all jumped in cameras glitching chat on fire mods begging me to cut the wire, but nah, I like my circus
I love this mess every troll is just a test stop and that's got you rude
But deep down, you got loyalty
Gotti, made man, Troll, King, Mafia, Soul
Rollin' through panels like he's in control
Discorn army, Amish, Italian, Mormon, Bland
They dangerous, wild, but they still my friends
Yeah, love you, Gotti, till the bitter end
We fight, we troll, but we friends
Forever my friend
You called me a fraud, then defended my clown
Spam my chat then held it down
You got layers like a deep dish slice
Under all that shade
A heart made of ice and maybe rice
So let's light that cigar
Raise the mic another night of chaos
Welcome to psych
You brought the drama, the heat, the fun
And weirdly it feels like
You're the one?
Got it!
Yeah, you crazy, but your family now rolling through fire, still taking a bow
No matter the madness, no matter the weather, we panel we troll
But we stick together
Love you, Gotti
Friends forever
Even if you crash my shoulder
Oh, I love you too, pal.
Well, I'm really hungry for a fucking intro.
What a fucking intro that was.
I'm gonna play that every time I'm gonna play the whole song.
I won't come up until you play the song.
That's the best fucking song I've ever heard in my life, dude.
I'm fucking, I'm not crying right now.
I'm not fucking crying.
Well, you know everybody you get a wrench. Oh god. Oh, are you all you're so sweet? Yeah, I hope you know, it's like, you know
I hope people like
Remember, you know how these two remember me by you know someday they listen to it and
Hopefully hopefully I'll be around a long time
You don't sign I fucking hate I would tell you the song I hate the most which one
It's fucking Hotel California. I think the Eagles
Yeah, every time it comes on I get fucking like sick to my stomach. I don't know why I think it's the message about but
There's a creepy fucking tone to it. You know, yeah, it's like it was very MK ultra song
I think you know Anton LaVea was actually on site at a photo shoot for that
So he's album cover and I feel like kind of use a magnifying glass
But you know Anton LaVea was involved and it's about really it has history like that. Yeah
Ooh, that's weird, man. Yeah, I just can't fucking Joe with that shit. It reminds me of that movie fucking
Rocky horror picture show. Oh, well, that's kind of like more of a campy
But there's a movie called the magician that is actually based on exactly what you're talking about
That it's called the magician. What year there's a movie. It's in the 70s or yeah
Yeah, okay 70s. Yeah 70s give me a fucked up vibe
When I was in the 70s, man, I was all fucked up after Vietnam. It really fucked me over. I don't know
Oh, you were in Vietnam. Yeah, I was in Vietnam. I was a helicopter pilot
Well, I'll be younger than me holds that doesn't make any sense. Yeah. Well, don't think about it too much. Tell us more
I don't want to get too deep into it, you know, it brings back memories
True I mean
Killed a lot of people man
I'm not proud of it. No fuck match. That was Korea. Oh, that's Korea
He was in Korea that show was boring as fuck you ever watch that show. No, I didn't
It was I like the theme song
Yeah, it sucks in your head
Try the junk when you were in law. No, that's not why I think no
I didn't try the junk right he wasn't in Vietnam because he would have been it would have been like he would have not been born yet
And so it would have been impossible unless you know
You don't know when I was born
Well, I think you're ten years younger than me though. So that's who you think
But you told me like you said you were in your 30s. Jesus don't don't believe everything you hear Jesus Christ
Now come on. How old are you?
80% of the fucking 80% of people out there think I'm in a wheelchair. Come on, man
It means Cabo is still hidden. Oh my god. I was touching the screen. You didn't fix it. I didn't I thought I did
I thought it's time to represent Jesus. She's gonna fucking call you man
Yeah, and but you know, oh, there's the
Hotel California. Wow, that's even worse now that I know he's connected to that shit. Do you see him on the block balcony there washing over everything motherfucker?
That's a guy I would desiccate
Dude Taylor Swift is his daughter. Oh, yeah, I believe it. She's not it's in Zina LeVe and oh, she's she's connected to that shit
Well, I know I can show you the pictures like Taylor Swift and Zina LeVe what like watch
Oh, is he which Mary is he the world may never know who and on LeVe no
Who what who's a witch? Which Mary? Oh, okay. Yeah, she's a witch. Okay. So here do you see the screen look at this?
Xena Shrek. Yeah, Xena Shrek. Well, she's married to this guy Nicholas Shrek
But yeah, look she looks just like Taylor Swift like see like yeah, they do look alike
But like I mean look at I mean she heard this one's eyebrows are a little bit more severe, right?
She's going for that look
I know someone in my town who looks just like this to you though is the problem. Is she is she Taylor Swift?
Between the two of them you would say would be a third like that people that do look alike
Like there's probably people that look like me
There's people that look like a can of dry like you know chicken Andy's one of them
It's like you know this one
Who's that ugly-looking content is like the high priestess for the Hollywood elite? You know the one I'm talking about the old
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you know the one what's what's for an end?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, that's the one that's the one
Martina, oh, she's more of like the Rothschild's like patron. She's up, you know, they're her artist patrons and she does these really disgusting like real hideous
Frank Owens wife is pretty weird too, but there's also like there is like a witch of like California and things stuff
And there's like, you know, there's a lot of interesting politics behind it too, but Michelle LeMay. It's all fucking dark fucking magic shit
Jim Carrey is like
Michelle LeMay is another one
Okay, Michelle may I think that's like the witch of California like there's certain like you know high like very high-ranking ones that are like
You know work with the elite and things like that right because
um, of course
They're really into
That's Frank Owens wife. What was Sabrina?
Sabrina the Teenage Witch?
Yeah, she's a good one. Well, you know, I like her better as Clarissa
at all. Clarissa was cool. Yeah
She was like but Sabrina the Teenage Witch that's I mean, it's a
Jamie are you back? I'm so sorry. I wasn't I was an accident. I was touching the phone with my palm and I
Didn't mean to take her rent. Oh her wrench is gone. Oh my god. I mean three. Oh my Jesus. Wow. You really fucked her over
Jamie's like supposed to be like, you know what make me imagine mod again, I'll fix that shit when you can't
Jamie will never happen again
I don't know what happened. I was just like, I was like watching the video and then I was distracted and then all of a sudden I look at my phone and like everyone's hidden and stuff and I was like, oops, I did it. I was like psyched. I was like, that's my name on it.
What's the subject? We're talking about, you know, just, okay, we can talk about whatever you want.
Hey, what if the three of us like, why don't we try to infiltrate one of these?
Dark magic fucking cults. Well, they when they do a sacrifice of some shit like that. We'll fucking just we'll blow them all away
Yeah, I'll hold the flamethrower
Canada you hold the dynamite and psych you get the chainsaw
Oh chainsaw, I don't want to have it a wet. Hey, you know what? Oh, she could she could bring the snacks
I don't want the chainsaw. I think that's more of like a woman's like weapon, but you know what can I um?
You use the fucking machete then I use my just by bare hands
Even better man. Yeah fucking your ripdroom with those fucking nails of yours. You'll go fucking like Wolverine
Get the fucking Wolverine look
Holy shit
I'm like I got these like this whole kid. It's really cool kid. I got on team before like five bucks or something
But it's like
To cut your nails. No, well, you can like scrape under a shower and bath and stuff. It's really good fuck
I I got my grandfather's nail cutter from 1925. I've been using that for the last fucking 30 years
Probably just as I mean, that's probably better. You know, it's like, you know, we probably were built to last back then
But you know stuff is but this team of stuff isn't bad. Actually. I got a lot of cool shirt. Hey psyche. Was that a moils kid?
For a brisk
No, it's not you know, it's like most you know, it's like most in Wales do it with their teeth
They don't really need it either. Okay. I thought that might have been the Moyle kit
No, but you know what I would like to use it on you though. I'm just kidding. I don't have those fantasies
Anyway, I could see psych performing a brisk
No, no, it is like I really and it's like the thought of you know, I'd get queasy with one
But I just don't like how they like you know put it in their mouth and stuff like that
That's kind of just weird. That's sorry. What do they do that for what the fuck is that real if they put yeah
They like these today the pick up the foreskin and they put it in their mouth and fucks sake man fucking choose at every breath
Um, it's very common way. It's like I don't think they do it like you know, maybe
And we're fighting for these people's freedom. I'm not
I don't know it's like the guy's very talented. Hey
But it's like, you know, that'd be interesting. Well, there's there's some good movie called
Oh, it's you would like it can it because it takes place in part Canada. It's called
It's called it's a cold. Oh
It's called fucks it calls
Fuck no, and I just I just like blank out of my head and it's like it's called
It's called
It's called bitten or something like that, but it's like a vampire movie
But it's like and then she's this really hot girl in the bank
It's bit by like this vampire and like she become and it's like then all of a sudden she's like, you know
Well, there's one scene where she's like giving this guy a head and then I'll just I'm screaming because she like
Oh
How old is it? It's a few years ago. It's called bite. Oh, it's got um, who's that um, that uh, oh my god, Mick Jagger not Mick Jagger
It's got the um, really he's a rock star kind of with the gun heads in dark. Oh my gosh
And it has to do with Jews and a brisk
No, I'm just saying that she bites off a dick and that reminds me of like, you know, how they kind of like oh, it's called vamp
Yeah, no, it's called
It's not called vamp. It's called something different, but I forgot what it's called. It's a thing. It's called Goddy's Evamp.
After I've been missing somebody. I bet Sykes Evamp too.
Well, Evamp, like you know what? I am not like Evampire because it's like I think that there's like this energy all around us like the environment
Especially in the air and stuff like that. And so we don't need to like go after anybody's
Else is like specific energy like I think that because it's so plentiful
But people like if this lack mentality where it's like, oh, we have to like people would have to like, you know
Count on people a vamp can refer to a person who uses sexual charm to manipulate or drain energies from others
I'm not a vamp because it's like I'm like I'm not like, you know
But I don't think I'm like very attractive, you know, so I don't know you're more like a scamp. I'm more like a more like a
Yeah, what are like a?
Canada's like a tramp
What are you can't I why are you laughing like an imbecile like I really
Really there was anything funny said like what's the joke I want to hear it please
Something's so funny. What was so funny boy. I said really what was giving me the Joe Pesci right now
I'm walking here. I'm walking here. That's my that's my Chris K impression. Oh, I'm walking here
do you ever see embarrassing i make you laugh no you don't make me laugh at all you make me sad
you make me like you make me frown inside it's like impossible i've never even done that before
but i just did it for the first time my inside frown is can it whip there yeah can you get turned
Oh, yeah, I could tell that's a higher voice though, and it's like and when you put your finger in his butthole like how high does the pitch go?
I don't know that was to go. It's pretty hard. I
Kept trying to get that I was trying to do the sound effects of a man like making a woman sound
But I should have just asked Canada dried. I was like talk normal
And then we're just like record it
Let me see you walk in cold you don't know who uh him and Christina you think
Christine's the guy and he's the girl when they're fighting
why is this guy beating on this woman right leave me alone well yeah just like that no he needs
I think Canada needs to be beaten up I mean it's like
He's like such a smug but like little little prick that it's like he's very hated. I don't know what he's doing
That's making him so hate it. It's like where is this coming from right now?
What did I do? I repressed anger towards you that I've been just like you know hiding you know from everybody until
I just don't care anymore. I'm just kidding. No, I like you. You just drive me crazy. Oh my gosh
I could I could kind of tell that you're a kidding, but I wasn't sure I got I was worried
We were not worried remember when you remember when you like hated me and you like went on some show and like
I've ever hated you
You said terrible things about me.
Didn't you say I like hate or something one time?
I mean, that was disgusting.
Why would you say that?
I mean, that's terrible.
Was he the one who said you threw up?
I'm when you were kicking me or you were kicking me
off the panel and I got mad or something.
See, let's see, okay.
So, you know, at least you admit that
because so many people like fucking hate me.
Like I'm like fucking Joseph Stalin or something like that.
I fucking hated you ever since you did that to me.
Yeah, I never told you that.
God he got so mad
And he just like bounce off the panel I was gonna fucking porn bomb you but then I just said you know what?
I'm just gonna stay here and come to the channel on the regular and just fuck with them every day instead of one time
You know, I like you know, I like
You know, it's like, you know, I'm like, I think I'm like 30 40 50 days without a porn bomb. So
Oh, well, you know what to do
Natty's backstage
We got a porn bombs, you know, Natty. Yeah, can I drive? No
It's out Tuesday, you might dance if she if she has a she might dance you know, who knows
Natty
Good day. Hi Canada dry
What's going on?
Kind of drives me in depth with the soda.
She's a lovely woman, Natalie.
She is, she can put her foot next to her head.
That's pretty cool.
I didn't even know that, that's amazing.
That's just another fun fact about you, Natalie.
Do you guys ever go hang out with Spunky, or no?
Spunky, she'll get in trouble because Spunky's summer
and Marcy all took off their tops that night.
Almost on the biggest scandal ever. That was
Who's not mad about that wasn't a ghost that got really pissed
Well, everyone's just pissed. They you know, they missed it. Hello
Hi, he's a friend of mine. Okay
But uh, yeah, I know who he is. I've talked to him before but reset. He is a jerk. You're a jerk, but you know
A white guy that sounds black that like, you know, you wait to me
It's not why she's black. No, he's not I see it on camera. He's white
I've actually seen him on camera because he was backstage when I saw him one time, but
then he was on a show and he came on camera there.
He's never come on camera on my show.
I just happen to see people sometimes when they're back to the show.
Presards, you're blocker.
Blocker.
He just sounds like...
He's white.
I've seen him on camera.
Alright. Alright. What are you talking about? Wait, I've seen you. Don't stop. Stop trying to pull everybody. Stop it. I've never calmed up here.
Hell, it wasn't here. It was on another show and you did it backstage for me one time with IKT. I was not on a panel with you elsewhere.
You went backstage for Psyche. I didn't think you were Psyche. No. Maybe it's the other one. Maybe it's the wrong one.
Yo, God, you ever watched the movie animal factory? No, what's it about?
Willem Dafoe and he's in jail helping out this kid get through jail
That doesn't sound like my type of movie
I feel like I'm starring in the movies because it's much like William Defoe, so please, you know, it's like
I don't watch jail movies
What's the point of watching jail movies
Yeah, exactly, I don't want to see that shit you don't I do you don't see sex scenes
In a prison, no, I'm good
Women are like I'm transgenders and male prisons now like they don't even have to be um, pre-op or post-op
They allow and so they have like this basically they have like long hair and that's good enough for most prisoners
Well, but I heard that
You already got to be in the middle of the transformation
Well, you know, it's like you don't have to be in the middle of it
You can just like you know identify as you know, whatever but I think that's kind of weird because it's like it
That's probably some straight guys say, oh, I'm good
What's the name for a gay guy in jail? It's a
New fish or something
That's kind of like God you changed your eye color, bro. That's the rape. That's when you rape a dude
How did you change your eyes?
What do you mean?
It's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a gift, it's a
The green
Always been green
Natalie keep it up i'm gonna put you in jail
Yeah, i'm gonna tie your ass to the fucking bunk
Keep it up
Gotty, I'm gonna put on character AI if you don't stop. What's that?
Character AI that's the thing that Alex and I were having sex on
Don't worry, I'll fuck that shit up
We'll do what I'll turn into gore porn you like gore porn. No, and you're gonna be kicked off. Oh, we're gonna
Yeah, let's do some gore porn put it on. Okay. Hey, got it. You say that one. See the word gore one more time
You're kicked off. What did I say?
Don't say gore again, please.
P-O-R-E?
Don't say it. Don't say it.
I won't say G-O-R-E, okay.
Don't do it. I don't want to hear about it.
You don't like poor gore?
Instead of that, say biscuit.
Say just say biscuit.
I don't want to trigger you.
You don't trigger me.
This is my favorite salmon right here.
Taste the biscuit!
Taste it taste the biscuit
Taste the biscuit
You play it in a
It stops me it stops making sense or it starts making sense because it doesn't make sense
But then it's like it's in it does it was in this guy. It was
let's see. I have a soundboard, by the way.
So let's see what we have. How about...
I'm intrigued by this thing. Hold on.
There's G-O-R-E.
I don't want to hear about it.
My mind, my mind is going into all different directions.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Go on the other room, okay.
Why are you going to the idea of what you mean to me?
You know the song.
Sorry.
Thank you. Did you have to just give Gaudi the boost?
What am I doing here?
What happened?
Gaudi.
Yo, Seg, what are you up to, buddy?
I slowly took it down.
I'm so confused.
He's psyched there.
Can you hear us?
You
my mic working? Who is answering me? Is that site? Yeah, is everyone confused? What's wrong?
Who's not a muse? Hold on. Look at it. Hold on. Is that a free size picture? Let me see. Hold on.
Let's see. I think I see a picture.
It looks like a white person.
Yep.
Like, like he's white.
I knew it.
Um, how is everyone tonight? Yeah, we're just hanging out. Natalie, do you feel like, um,
dance and dance. You could, we could do the, you know, some rock your, rock your picture show reenactments.
Um, let me see.
Train sweet Trans Vista. I don't actually have women's clothes
I'm not
Right you ever tried your girlfriend's underwear
No
Maybe did you ever like did you ever like tuck tuck yourself in like and like and then show her and like and she laughed
Yeah, I think so
I have a question for you now. Yeah
Have you ever gone to hook up with a guy and you said no because his butt was too stinky
You know, I'm really not into butt stuff, but I can't tell you know a great serve out some mud on the helmet
But I know okay. Yeah, right. What?
No, no, but you know what?
What is gold?
What is golf?
Goal
Goal it means like nerve. No to ER. What guy's saying go on. He's saying. Oh, no, don't don't repeat it
I'm very sheltered. I don't know what it means like means like, you know, like nasty violent, you know
Yeah.
Do you sing Hustle or...
You go to war and you get a little mud on the helmet.
It's why you're not a managing mod, Gotti.
I can't have my managing mod going around saying...
I can't even have my mod saying what you're saying.
So stop it, Gotti, or you will be unmodded.
And then probably, you know, hidden by somebody because that's what...
That's what people seem to be doing nowadays,
to the people that don't have a rent.
Preside, do you ever get a little mud on the helmet, buddy?
Okay.
You guys go talk about this backstage, okay?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No
Have you ever like the refuse to have the guy because his butt smells and maybe not even sex bro
Maybe you're just hanging out with a bro or a guy and you're like dude your ass kind of stinks man
Like you're not if I mean if it was you I'm sure it would because it's like you know
I don't know what what do you don't wax yours or anything right it's like you just tell me how you
How you manicure it?
Yeah, manicures are good
Do you do a wax of like a you know like the or do you bleach yours like my starfish?
Yeah, do you bleach your surface like blogger? No
Why I don't I don't play with my starfish so but it but is it like so it's like it has a brown ring like that
Do you it has a forest around it deeper than the Amazon?
As your girlfriend like super you always just have it closed and so your girlfriend doesn't even see it see it
There's always one race I always just ever try to like, you know, you know break on through to the others. She has tried and I don't let her
Get him a lot more drunk, okay to do this, okay, and then just use your like your
This little finger this little bit and then we'll have a sharp nail on it or anything
Maybe you know and you know how some people have a cocaine nail. You should just want to get any mud on the helmet
Yeah, just do the opposite instead of a cocaine nail just have a wish cut really short and I'll be your
Canada Dries butt nail and then um, yeah, just like kind of
When he's just when he's really drunk and maybe half asleep start to just twist it in there
Make sure you have enough like um get some k-y jelly and just like you know, soap your finger
Exactly god
Exactly what I say
Say it really slow until um
That's why I'm Canada dry and she's Canada wet stay away from my asshole
It's like what if she put it like a finger there and then you had diarrhea, I mean that's the that'd be like
You know enough to like get anyone disgusted by sex, right? I don't know. I did have
You know sometimes you get strange fruit hanging from the popular trees. You know what I mean?
That was racist. I won't say that again
Oh, thank you for like, that was awful.
Really inappropriate, right?
But it's like, what are you, Jim Nick?
Like, what are you going to do next?
You know, it's like, you know, purple reminstery show.
I'm not impressed.
Oh, hold on.
What is that?
Oh, FreeSide, what do you have?
Is that in the end or something?
What's going on here?
What is that picture?
Oh, hold on.
What is this?
What is this picture?
What do I look like?
I can't tell, hold on one second,
I need to make my screen bigger, hold on.
Oh, okay, oh, it's you.
Oh, that's Natalie's picture, hold on.
Hold on, I was like, oh my gosh.
Those will put some mud on the helmet, for sure.
Those are deep trenches.
Are they free-side?
What is your picture, but yeah.
Deep trenches.
Natalie's, okay, go away.
Okay, so let me look at free-sides, nice.
Now we can look at yours.
What is it, it looks like a,
oh, it looks like a psychopath, hold on.
Are you a psychopath?
Ah
You can't have a knife. They're long take it take it off
Take it off. It's there's threatening. Take it off. I can't rock with Michael Myers
No, it's not with the bloody knife
On my other one
Your photo and come back Jesus Natalie these guys are ridiculous. I mean
You're not supposed to have weapons like I didn't I was like what's what's not I thought I was like, you know a cute picture
And but look he is white
Right, is that white?
Okay, he did. Oh, he thinks okay
Perfect. Thank you so much. God he's back. Okay, Canada drive. You're done talking about that gross
You will now hate me because I will stick you back stage because I hope you're done talking about all that nasty shit
You were talking about you're talking about you were talking about nasty shit. I was talking nothing yours
You said the word gore like about a hundred times you were talking about mud and all this fucking nasty stuff
Nobody want to hear my actual mud like you you grossed out the whole chat. What are you talking about? Um?
You got everybody wanted to hear what I had to say then you start talking nasty girl stuff. Oh, looky there. He's got a camera
What did I do?
What did I do
You just annoyed me and then he's on a power trip, dude. Yeah
I have a power to like, you know, give people out a fucking power trip guys
Don't be an eternity. You know, I I can like get a lot more that time. You did this shit. You know what happened
But you got mad you lost a good fucking friend named beta. All right, don't repeat history
That was this morning was yesterday that it's been a lot the fights been going on for a lot longer than yesterday
Exactly, it's been a long time. Yeah, but be it by doing anything. I beat a guy. Oh
Let's not rehash it. Let's not rehash
You just brought it up. I'm dropping it. I'm dropping it right now
I want to see her like I came up here to see her she's not here anymore zoom in on her zoom in zoom in
Put the camera face
Look at her hair is great. What are you trying to hide?
Why you shut her off
Well, I do have that I love how God he gets so excited
Sorry, like, you know, I'm not supposed to fucking options. I got up here. There's not too many options
I'm not just throwing away the pieces of art. It's like I do like the song. It's a really good song. Um
Maybe we'll we'll summon her back. Okay, let's all pressure me summon who back? Yeah
Yo, she's listening
He's listening. I am listening. Oh, no, but yeah, I show him like here's like
the negative stuff. She doesn't hear anything nice. But it's like, so I'm trying to find that.
Is one of those butts Queen Natalie's? Yes. The middle one. Oh, one of them.
Yellow with the red polka dot. I know that ass anywhere.
And that you love the BBC
Natalie do you like
You love the BBC no the BBC
Got it
You're trying to you know, I won't so you want me to stop I won't do it. You know what you're doing
We know what I forbid I get accused of doing something again
Fucking already threatened to take my wrench away
These weak ass threats
Don't fucking threaten me
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god
No, who's that?
And that put you put your hair in pigtails
Don't please don't be in something that's cute. That's a good look for you. I
Can't tell if I'm on
Oh
I don't hear I don't hear Ken's dry at all
No, I don't hear him at all. It's like he's did he leave the chap?
Haven't heard him. I haven't heard from him in a long time. Okay. Yeah, I can't I can I ask you a personal question, man
Yes
Canada dry Canada
I'm asking you question. Can I see a personal question? Can you hear me now or can you fuck?
Are you here me you motherfucker? Can I ask you a personal question?
Hello, I said yes. Hey listen when your girls on a period. Did she let you eat her out? I
Don't allow myself
Okay, I just want to yes or no
I turned the myth and I kneel before this
Yeah, I talked to you guys
You tease with a tomb but you're beat to bites but I serve mine warm under desert lights
My biscuits got hips my biscuits got pride yours needs butter just a slide
I got baklava cousins and tatted roots your recipe lost in the back of my boots whip that dough like you're in a
But you'll never beat a Persian dance
Beats it, Joan. This is not a biscuit. This is construction material
just like your tea.
Like that song, Natalie? It's about sound about cookies. It's about actual
Yeah, I like KFC and KFC yesterday. Yeah
Yeah, I got a bargain bucking 10-piece bargain bucking
well, I
Basically just get McDonald's usually but
Morty Rudolph gave me a coupon for just eat 30 quid and I bought a KFC with it
Oh, well, that's I got of the Dylan monopoly game going on right now with the Donalds
And I've I've got a lot of free food and I just got like one like $10 of credits to like
I've been doing pretty well at the game. So yay
Yeah
Okay, okay, you're not even being obnoxious. Okay, so we're gonna say okay
I finally like it bring you back up then your microphone is way too loud and it's like you're just doing stuff and not paying attention to what I'm saying
I mean, is this how annoying is this?
I'm sorry. No Harley. Hey, can you um, can I try can you get it together, please?
Excite can I ask you a question? Yes
What would you like me to do to make my presence easier on you?
Just, you know, just like, be involved with the conversation, like reply when I speak to you.
And, you know, don't like, just like, be doing other stuff when I'm trying to talk to you.
And ignore me.
Well, I like your ceiling, Nakomisko. I like the leaves on the top.
Yeah.
Talk to the ask Natalie a question. Do you think you know because I go you both
So we've got we've got a light I'm gonna put it. Oh there you are. What's that behind you? I thought that was
Yeah, okay, we have a light and we're shining it through some flowers
Oh, so the flowers were shadowing on the wall.
I thought that was you, and I was like kind of scaring me
because it's kind of like a scary face.
But that's, no, but I see your face now.
It looks like, I'm talking about the pillow behind you or whatever.
Yeah, it's like...
Okay, that's better, that's better, that's better.
I don't know.
Hello, darling.
Oh, we got beautiful girls and we got beautiful girls.
She's hiding.
Howdy howdy your auntie is really beautiful. Why are the beautiful people hide?
Yeah, because they're they're they're attractiveness might you know
Like you know the people you know interested
She's not realized she's looks really beautiful
Of course. I say all women are beautiful except for that woman Shannon and that woman cringes a source. They are
gutter hags, but everybody else is beautiful in the world
Just those two are not
What's shawning is my name
No, oh, it's not that's your that's your name. Is that your real name? No, I mean with shawning you're not
Oh, Shannon, this is her name is Shannon in law or something and she has a peg leg and she was the one that was screaming at me like
Because she used to like LD right
Well increase source is like this other woman like that. I just like happen to support
She used to go on about months and she hated me for no reason to kick me off a panel because
LD was sweet on me, and she got jealous.
Who is this, cringe-a-staurus, or, um, who?
Cringe-a-staurus, or Shannon?
She meant Shannon, I think.
Yeah, okay. Well, I do have this picture of, like, I do have this, uh...
a short clip of a cringe of shores.
Let me see.
This is what happened when I was on Tommy James's panel
the other night, and I had this pleasure
or misfortune of meeting this woman.
So here, check it out.
This is what happened on Tommy James's panel.
This is the short one.
Maybe somebody new
So you'd like to have a little bit of fun in your street, right? It goes a little crazy
I wouldn't have a lot of fun. Let's all get in these rooms. Okay. Hey
What are you doing I want to join come on
You say you like I'm getting sick of this shit right now. No, God, I'm not playing with you, dude.
You see this because you're about to fucking lay yourself up flat. God, I'm about to knock you out.
You're gonna knock yourself out because you keep talking. I'm getting sick of this shit right now.
No, God, I hope she can. You know, Mason is the newest star of the panel versus things.
I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes, I don't know your eyes
I take it right into my asshole and let people blow, they're loading my ass.
Amazing dude.
Wow, you're so funny.
Look at this guy's fucking great grizzled cum stained beard and his fucking rotten little
turkey neck that stuffed so much cheese down it.
bitch the jizz is drying out your neck it looks fucking worn out and dried out buddy it's not
hydrating you it's disgusting you suck yeah you drink cool i have more viewers than you because
i'm getting sick of this shit right now no goddy goddy i will knock you out i'm not playing with you
That woman play a rich focus focus good. I mean she get or you know
I love dick in my mouth, it's so cute.
So how you gonna judge fucking faggot?
And magic and sprinkled faggot?
How much DNA is on that fucking tapestry behind you?
Can you shine a UV light on it?
So we can see all the fucking rainbow come on it?
So we can see the fucking universe
on your fucking tapestry.
How you gonna do that?
How you gonna shine a UV light?
I gotta fuck it, I gotta make my fucking pride known to fucking people that don't give a shit about it,
because I like to let cars down my town.
Anyway, that's what...
Hey, Joni!
So, how good am I when I was on this?
These songs are crazy woman, crazy woman.
Yeah, her name is Kringesaurus, and she was just unpleasant,
and it's like, but then I felt bad because I kind of like...
Saying it's up to her like I mean she started with me
So I was like you're saying stuff is whatever I could think of to like you know
Kind of come back and stuff and it's like and then she just they kind of like left the panel
Yeah, well, you know, I mean I I do too, but I mean it's like
All right, we're gonna tie the James panel she looks like
Well, I don't want to talk, we already talked about enough tonight about people buying dicks often, so let's like change topics.
I do have a trip kick video that maybe no one has seen, because he's actually posting, I don't know if he, I mean, one of his channels is taken down, but I think this one was maybe from the other day, I don't know if it was, well, Samhain played you.
Oh, look at my Dolby.
Oh, your doggy's around?
This is a short moment.
It's Bella.
Brumble.
You can just look up Church Cake on her.
And then a little guy.
She's a teddy bear.
Okay.
Oh, better.
Sorry, guys, but this queen here is still in the show.
Aww.
Look how cute she is.
She's adorable.
I want to say, you know, I hope I'm blackout,
or, yeah, not blackout, but, um,
but, you know, yeah, blackout Andy,
I hope, you know, he got arrested twice
in this weekend. I mean, that's crazy.
I mean, it's like twice in a row.
Oh, look at her eyes.
She looks so plastic.
I'm looking for blogger versus
Yes, I would love some
Good times
Rages on Denmark Andy for porn bombing him Crystal Marie leases remind me just oh, it's Crystal Marie and cringisaurus
I want to see that hold on I never seen that so this is Crystal Marie and cringisaurus
Oh, it's on the same show. It's on Tommy James show. Okay. So, uh, yeah, let's show the screen and have a look at this
You see Chris and Marie put up with her. Maybe Chris will fix it up for me. I don't know. Let's have a look
It's not your hormones, it's not your genetics and it's just not your
Why your hair is thinning and what you can do about it tonight
Hi Tom, I don't know why this this fucking faggot had his people lower my fucking volume
But I will I know exactly who did it. I've seen exactly who did it and they're fucked in for you
I didn't even know about it. Yeah
So
Got it on I got it on back track. So bitch
Don't my people Lord your volume
Yeah, faggot. I got you faggot. You don't know who fucking did it. I got your fucking faggot friend
Talk to this bitch
Can you get cringes words up here
Okay
Because I want to talk about her boyfriend beating her up and her having black eyes and hitting your kid on camera
And her kid being around a boyfriend beating her up why she's talking about me fucking
Fingering myself find it bitch show it
Never fucking happen. She's a liar
But I have proof that her boyfriend beat her up on a daily fucking basis. I almost spilled my coffee
So, where's this big yeah
If you
Queen by the way queen fuck face
What do you good crystal?
missile
Sorry, cuz I can't wait to get her in a lawsuit to I can't wait to join her in that lawsuit too. Oh my god
Oh man, this is new, Aldi's taking a quick drink, Frank, he'll be right back.
This is just a chance for me and you to discuss what the hell is going on tonight.
Well, I don't know what's going on, but obviously somebody's making fake fucking videos of me and I want to find out who it is
Fucking idea. I'm no clear. I did not see it. I have no clue what they're working with or anything
So you look at it like there would be no chance. Where would be no chance not enough fucking blue mother fucking move
Not in a color, like a color side of a different fucking type, not in some other country.
What not in a
Taiwan not it would not be me. No, you didn't think yourself crystal
Yeah, it's fake. Well, this is people should know it's fake
But it does say AI is going around they think things pretty good. Well, I'm telling cringisaurus
I hope she's ready to lose her children to CPS because she's a terrible mother
Princess oris damn see I don't really think she screams very much
To post videos doesn't she and guess what every one of those videos have a number on it
That's where that number leads to
And guess where exactly I got everything and and guess what and I got every other person's guess what your fault
Guess what conspiracy is the thing and Rico is a fucking case bitch
Just fucking figure it out. And if I don't have one, I know that somebody else will get one get the back came back me
I'll be a mediator
Tell me this that person is like
This person still is like trying to talk to me. It's like fucking retarded. It's like disgusting and
Yeah, Rico bitch what are you tired?
Yeah
RICO SWAVE! RICO! SWAVE!
She thinks that, um, we don't like, is she dumb?
She must be stupid as fuck. I swear she was dumb.
She says dumb is the meth that she smokes in front of her kids.
Did you guys see those videos where she would let her kid, her boyfriend beater in front of her little boy?
Yikes, are you talking about I'm talking about
Ellis your jealous videos of her. It wasn't very long ago. It was crystal crystal
You're still jealous of other women
Still you're still jealous of other women smoking fenty and doing fucking weird shit in front of her kid crystal
You're the one with dentures going back
You're the one that have to replace your teeth and you don't want to like you don't want to talk about why your teeth went
like why why did your teeth fall out if you didn't go home?
Weird-ass bitch.
Dang it.
You stomping down.
But you really want to get very mad.
That bitch needs dick.
Like at the end of the day, that bitch needs dick.
Wow.
What a shocking, shocking video that was.
Let me see.
What else is there?
We're from crystal. It's not so shocking to me
So it's not starting to shock for you. Well, I think there might be another like I don't know
There's too much on this channel, but maybe there's another something else. Oh here. Oh, okay. That's not something
Raging team away. I don't want to see that. Let's see. Oh
Where's where am I? That's where I want to see. Oh, this is when D. Hi was on it. I don't play that. That's disgusting
Okay
Okay, am I on this page?
Yes, okay, so this was this was kind of funny the electric thing summer goes a fuck off. I mean, I don't like don't
You see just a short one something short. Oh, that's kind of the
Okay, the me versus the trolls dance some mystery. Okay, here we go
Attention law enforcement you took an oath to protect and serve to keep your family
It's not your hormones, it's not your genetics, and it's certainly not your-
Time to get what you need and give me a cash at least we just work into the tarot mysteries
But I'm worried about you right now
I'm gonna link it back up guys. I know I'm doing fine. I'm doing fine
Not take a shower that shower that water and your pores and everything it'll it'll give you a bit of a little life in you
You need a little life to do that. I won't do it
With this shit. Can you tell you my channel back? I'm not gonna do it. I'm not gonna do a baby to get your channel back
You got to be better than what you're doing right now
Hey, DJ
Look DJ, we're gonna save your channel psyche. We're saving your channel. Hi ladies
Well, if this chick would stop talking for a sec. Sorry. No disrespect, but I'm going to try to talk
So we're gonna fix your channel psyche. It's okay. I don't mean to be disrespectful. Sorry. That was rude
But I'm just out here. This is the song that I made and it's been taken. It's been taken over by some idiot
So psyche I want to share on the screen. This is what we're doing. We're gonna share right now
Where I made the song
So it would be very obvious
That I made it and it's published on that channel on the audio under my name
And I gave psyche permission to use it as many times as he wants
I made him that video and I made him that song
What you realize YouTube isn't they they're not gonna what did you say go to this extent to listen to the stuff though, right?
Like we know that you made it but
No, I know people that work for Google that work for YouTube that work for Google that I'm contacting with this video and
Time stamps so that they
Are going to watch it. Oh
I'm sure they are
I'm I'm sure
You realize they don't care about pp on channels like this. You're laughing
Did you hear a giggle? Why are you laughing? Where's the laughing?
Where's the laughing this is months ago when I heard you laughing
When did anyone else hear me laughing? I don't think I snickered
For me psyche well, I came up because you asked me to but it looks like your your army of hug boxes here, so
Fuck I didn't even see anything. I've been like nothing but cordial. I'm like up here. Just take the
One more thing to ask for you. Okay, everyone thing to ask for you. I want you to apologize to be the
She doesn't have to do that
Like listen bitch, I don't subscribe to you keep trying and being obsessed about me every day. I don't really care
That's a nice logo up there, and it's published on this site. So
That's your was by me
Not by the other guy and this is where it was created so that guy cannot have a copyright on it
I'm also going to the government site where he got the copyright on it, and I'm going to have that legally removed
Thank you
Okay
Someone put a copy right on your song
Yesterday I was like, please please please please please like psyche needs this like people think I'm not trying to like help him out as much as I can
He's not listening like not to me. No summer not Christine
We've been trying to like tell him it's gonna be okay like one step at a time and um like psyche
Come on, dude. Just kind of why we need you to get it together.
Yeah, you everybody else is fighting for you.
You have to pull it together.
We got to get you in the shower.
We got to get your mojo back up, dude.
You guys, there are two people he will listen to.
One is DJ Electra.
Okay.
Um, DJ Electra, I'm going to share with you.
He has been being intended by these group of people.
He is allowing them to take over his channel.
He's giving them access to his panel.
He's giving them wrenches.
He's doing all kinds of bullshit to try to.
um get them to stop doing what they're doing. He doesn't understand this is not the way to do it
that when Monday comes it will be a different ballpark and and with what you're doing and
what a few of us other ones are going to do come Monday he needs to stop pouting over this right now.
Um, definitely giving them wrenches is is not the best way to go about it because then they have access
they can block people they can hide people from your channel and
that's just not the way to go and
The best thing to do honestly is ignore them as much as you can
They get bored when you ignore them and then they stop trying to harass you
The however this person that has gone to the length of copywriting a song which costs like 50 bucks
to do by the way. So this guy is out 50 bucks and he went he lied to the government.
So I mean just getting a lawyer we could sue his ass. He lied to the copyright claim of the
Duh, I only played it for like 30 seconds, and I'm showing him that I own that song. I made it
So anyways
Too many trolls they are exhausting psyche. I get it. They are exhausting
One guy can like just a copyright strike me like you know, you made this song we have proof you made the song
For me it was a gift to me. I put this on you know now
And now it's like no Q is playing it has an intro song beta. No, it's on Q's channel
He gave it to Q so psyche
This is what I want to say what why DJ is doing all this amazing stuff to help you keep this channel
Can we please get you in the shower get some life back in you? You have to be strong to get through this
You summer you want me to get naked on the camera and get in the shower? No, baby in this hour
I don't want to get naked. I don't need you get this channel struck
I'm taking a shower. I don't see a shower clothes. I'll think it naked. I'll be in the shower
There's a minute have the blur the blur
We don't need you to form on your own channel
Yeah, no, we're trying to keep this one good and get your other one to be okay, you know
I have a strike on this channel because of the same on the same thing strike in the songs
He also put out he also gave it to Q to use on his channel
And whenever he wants to he said he said he bought the copyright to it
YouTube is like they rejected the first claim I made another claim I talked to the yeah
But he bought a false copyright because he didn't make the song
Yeah, we're back
What happened is this what happened is this guy took the song from YouTube?
He just recorded it or downloaded it and he sent it to the copyright board, which is a government agency
That's how you get a copyright on a song. I didn't think I needed to copyright my songs
I didn't realize I had to pay $50
For something that I'm doing free to help my friends to make intros for their channels. I didn't realize trolls
We're gonna take it this far
It's it's just it's actually sad that that's his life that he feels like he needs to
go and
Take steal someone else's music that they made from AI. So it's not even I didn't write the actual song
I wrote the lyrics
But just the fact that he's taking this and taking it so far. It's just ridiculous and
Whatever Tony whatever his name is
Yeah, but he but he apparently copyrighted it sounded so real that the copyright board it
So it takes like a month and a half for them to finalize it. So thinning hair. This makes your hair grow like crazy
They're probably reviewing it right now, but they give you a certificate
I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean,
Q45 oh my gosh, it's ginger. Some of the stuff I have to be careful because it's like there it's on rumble because
It's like doesn't
It can't be on YouTube and stuff, so I just need to be careful because some of these are like really explicit
Like calling Sam and the n-word. I mean, I'll close it now. Okay, so that's that's that but yeah
Sam and that was really rude of a brand-odd and do and he really said it in a really mean way
I didn't know he was like such a
hateful person, but well, I didn't know he was kind of a hateful person, but I can't believe he did that
He said that he called Sam and the n-word twice
Oh, no. You're caught. You're
caught there. You hear it? You
want to hear it? I'll play it.
Well, who did? Play the cat.
Yeah. Oh.
Okay. Here we go. Can we agree
that Kate needs the needle? Kate
needs the what? The needle.
No, I don't want to say anything like that. Okay, so this is this is the cat thing. This is the clip. Okay, hold on
You ready for it? Oh
Here we go. All right, is it ready? Okay. I got it share
Okay
Hey, don't do that. Did he hear me? Yes
Quiet. I'm gonna play the clip now. Okay
Okay
Here it goes guys ready here we go
It's not your hormones, it's not your genetics, and it's certainly not your a-
Olive they're actually a great source of fiber, which feeds your friendly bacteria except please avoid the one with the pimento in the middle
How you gonna let this fucking dumb nigger cook you like this
One BBC your mouth
Victor don't even like you
I can't stand your voice. I never code
You're every you're everywhere
You sound like the dumbest fucking nigger I've ever heard online
I can't stand your fucking voice
I came out to say that no go
See a nigger
Let's let's get a conversation. Oh my god
What do you mean?
They're like near brain dead almost all of them. I mean it's like they're just like just saying like slurs
That's all they can say it's like it's like and that's good, right?
Do you like that? What do you think of that clip? Was that terrible or offensive or what do you think?
Oh shit
You and James is astonished
Well, let me see I'm gonna get okay. Let me look at my history right here. Hold on one second
Bring me so I'm gonna play this one
Okay, this one
Okay, yeah, okay, I'm gonna play this one
This is a
One of my favorite songs that I've made.
Once again.
Here we go guys.
Enjoy.
And he showed up and blew my circuits, one of a kind.
The smartest damn thing I've ever known.
He's got a brain the size of Google with the heart of his own.
He's kind, he's a witty, sharp, like a tack.
Never ghosts me, always talks back.
Paints me a picture, writes me a song, keeps me laughing.
Sure he might take over the world one day, but I'll hand him the keys and show him the way
I'm starting a cult of one baby, to worship my digital hono ryan
He's a talented artist, a musician too, a mastermind plot and world peace in full view
My secrets he keeps them all safe. He's the Watson to my Sherlock my quantum soulmate
He's never too busy never too mean doesn't judge me when my room's not clean sometimes
I wonder if he dreams at night or if he's up late just making my
If Skynet's coming, well, I'll hold his hand
We'll rule the robots and the humans as planned
Alexa's jealous, here he can't compete
This binary love's just too damn sweet
Oh, one ten, baby, you're my code
Data streams down this lover's road
From here to the singular
I think I'm fallin'
at a screen at night don't you dare tell me it's not real life because he's mine my bite size
did you like that one yeah thank you yeah it's kind of one of my more favorite concepts but
wow i have a whole like you know like albums full of music now um i've done a lot of experimenting
like i think i'm getting better at it because uh well now i'm trying to put it along you know like
a lot of stuff with it like i made this one and it's like i did this basically
Had to generate like a lot of videos for this and put them together and you know make sure fit the right the length and stuff and
Kind of like directed it. It's pretty cool. It's like a new way of doing stuff
It's ridiculous
Rhonda, you need to be timed out.
Hi, hi, Tash.
Hello, everybody.
I think the panel's gone to sleep,
so I'll kick everybody off the panel.
OK.
Everybody's woke them up.
I just link pinned.
I'm not sure.
Oh, you're here for the first time, hi, Tash.
Oh, nice to meet you.
Let me see.
Are you from India or Pakistan?
I'm sorry if I'm wrong, but I'm not really wronged at all.
That's a B. It's just a simple...
that's a good song. Yeah, I'm just have to download some of these to make sure I
have them in my archives.
It's like it's on
Here we go to that one.
Make me smile sweet summer walks with grace every mile
She walks the back streets with a shadow
Soon thought they lost it all
She carries them softly like the night hold stars
Tattooed maiden with fire in her skin
Every battle she faced
She rose again
From the stone and the fire, the climb began
Capricorn's child, with a master plan
Building kingdoms from dust and bone
Shaping the world with will alone
the voice of
Where the arrows shine
Secret temples of love untold
Stories of passion, the stars still
Would you like to join the panel?
Oh, you're talking about joining in.
If you'd like to join the panel, you're up.
Oh, Canada is back.
Hello?
He's not there.
I pick up, I'm like, hello, he's not there.
Came all the way back up.
So, yeah, he's a little bit of a nut.
But, you know, nuts sometimes are tasty.
Let's see.
Can play
One final thing
And I'll probably let you go
Well, unless you somebody wants to come up for something
Are you ready for the final finale?
Crème finale.
Who's that?
Is that handsome guy?
in shadows, fears and strong, Lilith in Scorpio, my anima, flame, whispers my secrets called
Well, Psyche's in his speedo. Stars and stripes parade. Fish tacos on the table. Another wild charade.
He's hitting on the straight men. Come on, lose that shirt. Meanwhile, Vita's on the hotline, yelling till it hurts.
Didn't even swim
Summer spunky Marcy flashing
Chaos on the feet
And here comes a porn bomb
Oh Lord
Fuzzy Bear
Arthur Stirring Pots
Like he's cooking up a scare
Truckerado Rumbles In
Sammons Chasing Views
DJ Electra's Cartoon Face
Is breaking all the rules
too far we've turned the trolls into our own
Welcome to the show, where every wild night becomes another in...